const arrayOfDecks = [
  {
    id: 1,
    user_id: 5,
    name: 'React',
    description: 'React based flashcards set',
    category_id: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    user_id: 2,
    name: 'Node',
    description: 'NodeJS based flashcards set',
    category_id: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    user_id: 1,
    name: 'Postgresql',
    description: 'PostgreSQL based flashcards set',
    category_id: 2,
  },
];

const arrayOfDecksWithCards = [
  { 1: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10] },
  { 3: [2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 11, 12] },
  { 8: [2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 13, 14] },
];

const arrayOfFlashcards = [
  {
    id: 1,
    user_id: 1,
    question: 'Q1',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A1',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A1'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    user_id: 2,
    question: 'Q2',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A2',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A2'],
    public: true,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    user_id: 3,
    question: 'Q3',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A3',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A3'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    user_id: 4,
    question: 'Q4',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A4',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A4'],
    public: true,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    user_id: 5,
    question: 'Q5',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A5',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A5'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    user_id: 6,
    question: 'Q6',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A6',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A6'],
    public: true,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    user_id: 7,
    question: 'Q7',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A7',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A7'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    user_id: 8,
    question: 'Q8',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A8',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A8'],
    public: true,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    user_id: 9,
    question: 'Q9',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A9',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A9'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    user_id: 9,
    question: 'Q9',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A9',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A9'],
    public: true,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    user_id: 10,
    question: 'Q10',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A10',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A10'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    user_id: 11,
    question: 'Q11',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A11',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A11'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    user_id: 12,
    question: 'Q12',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A12',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A12'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    user_id: 13,
    question: 'Q13',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A13',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A13'],
    public: false,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    user_id: 14,
    question: 'Q14',
    url: '/',
    answer: 'A14',
    all_answers: ['decoy1', 'decoy2', 'decoy3', 'A14'],
    public: false,
  },
];
